<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on Hi, I&#39;m Phi.</title>
    <link>/categories/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on Hi, I&#39;m Phi.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>March 2020</title>
      <link>/playlists/march-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/march-2020/</guid>
      <description>A lot of new music being released despite COVID-19. Might be the only thing keeping me sane during these crazy times.
 Car Seat Headrest - Can&amp;rsquo;t Cool Me Down Dirty Projectors - Overlord Shabazz Palaces - Fast Learner (feat. Purpel Tate Nate) Theophilus London - Whiplash (feat. Tame Impala) Phoebe Bridgers - Garden Song Waxahatchee - Lilacs King Princess, Channel Tres - Hit The Back (Channel Tres Remix) HAIM - The Steps Porches - Patience U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2020</title>
      <link>/playlists/february-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/february-2020/</guid>
      <description>The last song on this playlist was shared to me from an Irish friend who has exquisite taste in music. Hi Aoife!
 Donny Benét - Girl of My Dreams Tame Impala - Lost in Yesterday Caribou - Home Thundercat - Black Qualls (feat. Steve Lacy &amp;amp; Steve Arrington) Real Estate - Paper Cup (feat. Sylvan Esso) Against All Logic - Deeeeeeefers Khruangbin &amp;amp; Leon Bridges - Midnight yllwblly - The Youngest Child Avalon Emerson - One More Fluorescent Rush Postcard Versions - Fence Response   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2020</title>
      <link>/playlists/january-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/january-2019/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretty heads down preparing for data science interviews (side note: HIRE ME!), so a more outsized presence from electronic music this month. The last one in particular was a favorite of my old flatmates in Berlin. But of course, a requisite appearance by Phoebe Bridgers.
 Lewsberg - The Smile Ethan Gruska - Enough for Now (feat. Phoebe Bridgers) Japanese Breakfast - Essentially Sidney Gish - Impostor Syndrome Surf Curse - Disco Ryley Walker - Spoil with the Rest Aquaserge - Tour du monde Mark Giuliana, Kesswa - BUD (Shigeto Mix) DAVID AUGUST - A Golden Rush (feat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/december-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/december-2019/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m starting to source music from a broader set of sources (television, film). I recently saw the film &amp;ldquo;Jojo Rabbit&amp;rdquo; and fell in love with the music choices. I added a couple songs from the film onto this playlist. These songs are actually German versions of old hits. Additionally, I&amp;rsquo;m adding old and new tunes together. Previously I tried to stick to new releases, but I found that quest to daunting at times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/november-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/november-2019/</guid>
      <description>A lot of Phoebe Bridgers in this one, sorry. What can I say, she&amp;rsquo;s the dream.
 Matt Berninger, Phoebe Bridgers - Walking on a String HAIM - Now I&amp;rsquo;m In It Phoebe Bridgers - Georgia Lee Wovoka Gentle - 1,000 Thousand Opera Singers Working In Starbucks Phoebe Bridgers, Fiona Apple - 7 O&amp;rsquo;Clock News / Silent Night People Club - Who I Call My Baby Hatchie - Her Own Heart Fazerdaze - Shoulders Long Beard - Getting By girl in red - i wanna be your girlfriend   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/october-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/october-2019/</guid>
      <description> Danny Brown - uknowhatimsayin? (feat. Obongjayar) Vagabon - Every Woman Pinegrove - Phase Earl Sweatshirt - EL TORO COMBO MEAL (feat. Mavi) FKA twigs - sad day Michael Kiwanuka - You Ain&amp;rsquo;t The Problem Frank Ocean - In My Room Caribou - Home The Game - Stainless (feat. Anderson .Paak) Vetiver - Lost (In Your Eyes)   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/september-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/september-2019/</guid>
      <description> (Sandy) Alex G - Southern Sky Pinegrove - Moment Metronomy - Walking In The Dark JPEGMAFIA - Jesus Forgive Me, I Am A Thot Soccer Mommy - lucy Local Natives - When Am I Gonna Lose You Big Thief - Not Nick Cave &amp;amp; The Bad Seeds - Ghosteen Allah-Las - In The Air Wilco - Before Us   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/august-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/august-2019/</guid>
      <description> Faye Webster - Jonny Ezra Furman - I Wanna Be Your Girlfriend Surfer Blood - Around Your Sun Angel Olsen - All Mirrors HAIM - Summer Girl Clairo - Bags Jay Som - Nighttime Drive Frankie Cosmos - Wanna Go Bombay Bicycle Club - Eat, Sleep, Wake (Nothing But You) Lana Del Rey - Doin&amp;rsquo; Time   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/july-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/july-2019/</guid>
      <description> Polo &amp;amp; Pan - Nana Tame Impala - Borderline Peggy Gou - Starry Night Bon Iver - Faith Jay Som - Tenderness Snail Mail - The 2nd Most Beautiful Girl in the World park hye jin - I DON&amp;rsquo;T CARE Devandra Banhart - Katori Ongaku Frankie Cosmos - Window Weyes Blood - Everyday   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/june-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/june-2019/</guid>
      <description> Thom Yorke - I Am a Very Rude Person Bon Iver - Hey, Ma Freddie Gibbs - Palmolive (feat. Pusha T. &amp;amp; Killer Mike) Denzel Curry - RICKY Lucy Dacus - Forever Half Mast Cate le Bon - Daylight Matters Mac DeMarco - Nobody Vampire Weekend - Sunflower (feat. Steve Lacy) Julia Jacklin - Don&amp;rsquo;t Know How to Keep Loving You SASAMI - Free (feat. Devandra Barnhart)   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/may-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/may-2019/</guid>
      <description> Stella Donnelly - Boys Will Be Boys Better Oblivion Community Center - Dylan Thomas JID - Skrawberries (feat. BJ The Chicago Kid) Tyler, The Creator - EARFQUAKE Anderson .Paak - Make It Better (feat. Smokey Robinson) Nilüfer Yanya - Paralysed Toro Y Moi - Ordinary Pleasure Billie Eilish - bury a friend Aldous Harding - The Barrel A$AP Rocky - Sundress   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>