<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi, I&#39;m Phi.</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hi, I&#39;m Phi.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>February 2020</title>
      <link>/playlists/feb-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/feb-2020/</guid>
      <description>The last song on this playlist was shared to me from an Irish friend who has exquisite taste in music. Hi Aoife!
 Donny Benét - Girl of My Dreams Tame Impala - Lost in Yesterday Caribou - Home Thundercat - Black Qualls (feat. Steve Lacy &amp;amp; Steve Arrington) Real Estate - Paper Cup (feat. Sylvan Esso) Against All Logic - Deeeeeeefers Khruangbin &amp;amp; Leon Bridges - Midnight yllwblly - The Youngest Child Avalon Emerson - One More Fluorescent Rush Postcard Versions - Fence Response   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>January 2020</title>
      <link>/playlists/january-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/january-2019/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been pretty heads down preparing for data science interviews (side note: HIRE ME!), so a more outsized presence from electronic music this month. The last one in particular was a favorite of my old flatmates in Berlin. But of course, a requisite appearance by Phoebe Bridgers.
 Lewsberg - The Smile Ethan Gruska - Enough for Now (feat. Phoebe Bridgers) Japanese Breakfast - Essentially Sidney Gish - Impostor Syndrome Surf Curse - Disco Ryley Walker - Spoil with the Rest Aquaserge - Tour du monde Mark Giuliana, Kesswa - BUD (Shigeto Mix) DAVID AUGUST - A Golden Rush (feat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/december-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/december-2019/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m starting to source music from a broader set of sources (television, film). I recently saw the film &amp;ldquo;Jojo Rabbit&amp;rdquo; and fell in love with the music choices. I added a couple songs from the film onto this playlist. These songs are actually German versions of old hits. Additionally, I&amp;rsquo;m adding old and new tunes together. Previously I tried to stick to new releases, but I found that quest to daunting at times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>November 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/november-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/november-2019/</guid>
      <description>A lot of Phoebe Bridgers in this one, sorry. What can I say, she&amp;rsquo;s the dream.
 Matt Berninger, Phoebe Bridgers - Walking on a String HAIM - Now I&amp;rsquo;m In It Phoebe Bridgers - Georgia Lee Wovoka Gentle - 1,000 Thousand Opera Singers Working In Starbucks Phoebe Bridgers, Fiona Apple - 7 O&amp;rsquo;Clock News / Silent Night People Club - Who I Call My Baby Hatchie - Her Own Heart Fazerdaze - Shoulders Long Beard - Getting By girl in red - i wanna be your girlfriend   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>October 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/october-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/october-2019/</guid>
      <description> Danny Brown - uknowhatimsayin? (feat. Obongjayar) Vagabon - Every Woman Pinegrove - Phase Earl Sweatshirt - EL TORO COMBO MEAL (feat. Mavi) FKA twigs - sad day Michael Kiwanuka - You Ain&amp;rsquo;t The Problem Frank Ocean - In My Room Caribou - Home The Game - Stainless (feat. Anderson .Paak) Vetiver - Lost (In Your Eyes)   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/september-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/september-2019/</guid>
      <description> (Sandy) Alex G - Southern Sky Pinegrove - Moment Metronomy - Walking In The Dark JPEGMAFIA - Jesus Forgive Me, I Am A Thot Soccer Mommy - lucy Local Natives - When Am I Gonna Lose You Big Thief - Not Nick Cave &amp;amp; The Bad Seeds - Ghosteen Allah-Las - In The Air Wilco - Before Us   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/august-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/august-2019/</guid>
      <description> Faye Webster - Jonny Ezra Furman - I Wanna Be Your Girlfriend Surfer Blood - Around Your Sun Angel Olsen - All Mirrors HAIM - Summer Girl Clairo - Bags Jay Som - Nighttime Drive Frankie Cosmos - Wanna Go Bombay Bicycle Club - Eat, Sleep, Wake (Nothing But You) Lana Del Rey - Doin&amp;rsquo; Time   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/july-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/july-2019/</guid>
      <description> Polo &amp;amp; Pan - Nana Tame Impala - Borderline Peggy Gou - Starry Night Bon Iver - Faith Jay Som - Tenderness Snail Mail - The 2nd Most Beautiful Girl in the World park hye jin - I DON&amp;rsquo;T CARE Devandra Banhart - Katori Ongaku Frankie Cosmos - Window Weyes Blood - Everyday   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/june-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/june-2019/</guid>
      <description> Thom Yorke - I Am a Very Rude Person Bon Iver - Hey, Ma Freddie Gibbs - Palmolive (feat. Pusha T. &amp;amp; Killer Mike) Denzel Curry - RICKY Lucy Dacus - Forever Half Mast Cate le Bon - Daylight Matters Mac DeMarco - Nobody Vampire Weekend - Sunflower (feat. Steve Lacy) Julia Jacklin - Don&amp;rsquo;t Know How to Keep Loving You SASAMI - Free (feat. Devandra Barnhart)   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2019</title>
      <link>/playlists/may-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/playlists/may-2019/</guid>
      <description> Stella Donnelly - Boys Will Be Boys Better Oblivion Community Center - Dylan Thomas JID - Skrawberries (feat. BJ The Chicago Kid) Tyler, The Creator - EARFQUAKE Anderson .Paak - Make It Better (feat. Smokey Robinson) Nilüfer Yanya - Paralysed Toro Y Moi - Ordinary Pleasure Billie Eilish - bury a friend Aldous Harding - The Barrel A$AP Rocky - Sundress   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Data Frames in Pandas, Part 2</title>
      <link>/blog/working-with-data-frames-in-pandas-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/working-with-data-frames-in-pandas-part-2/</guid>
      <description>In part one of this series, I covered how to replicate much of the tidyverse functionality in Python and pandas. In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll go over how to do basic plotting with matplotlib and seaborn, as those seem to be the two most commonly used Python plotting libraries. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to replicate plots that I can easily do in ggplot2, the graphics package in R.
I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of ggplot2 in R because it creates a consistent &amp;ldquo;grammar&amp;rdquo; for which all graphics must adhere to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working with Data Frames in Pandas, Part 1</title>
      <link>/blog/working-with-data-frames-in-pandas-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/working-with-data-frames-in-pandas-part-1/</guid>
      <description>In the past few months, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on beefing up my data wrangling skills with Python and the pandas library. Coming primarily from an R background, I&amp;rsquo;m a huge advocate of the tidyverse family of packages (namely, dplyr for wrangling, tidyr for tidy data sets, and ggplot2 for plotting), from the great and powerful Hadley Wickham. For me, these packages heavily simplify data manipulation by providing a common &amp;ldquo;grammar&amp;rdquo; for which to operate on data, and for enabling method chaining using the pipe operator (%&amp;gt;%).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resampling Methods</title>
      <link>/blog/resampling-methods/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/resampling-methods/</guid>
      <description>Suppose you are asked the following question:
&amp;ldquo;You have a sequence \(X = {X_1, &amp;hellip;, X_N}\) of independently and identically distributed random variables drawn from the same unknown distribution. How would you estimate the variance of the sample median?&amp;rdquo;
This question was posed to me in a recent data science interview. At the time I didn&amp;rsquo;t know the answer because I was pretty unfamiliar with computational statistics. But now, as a form of self-atonement, I want to answer this question in detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing Decision Boundaries</title>
      <link>/blog/visualizing-decision-boundaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/visualizing-decision-boundaries/</guid>
      <description>Note: I&amp;rsquo;m going to be doing a series of posts on interesting algorithms that I&amp;rsquo;ve either used in the past or intend to use in the future. Most of this stuff is fairly new to me or something I haven&amp;rsquo;t explored in depth, so please correct me if I am entirely off base. I fully believe that trying to explain a concept engenders a deeper understanding of said concept, so this is mostly a training tool for me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Albums of 2019</title>
      <link>/blog/my-favorite-albums-of-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/my-favorite-albums-of-2019/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m always a bit relunctant to write &amp;ldquo;End of Year&amp;rdquo; lists, since I&amp;rsquo;m hardly an authority on musical taste. I&amp;rsquo;m not a musician by any stretch of the imagination, nor have I ever really attempted to learn an instrument, so I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say I could accurately judge the technical qualities of the albums either.
Then there is the whole creative aspect of the matter. How can one measure something that is inherently creative?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2014-2015 Bundesliga Season, Visualized</title>
      <link>/blog/2014-2015-bundesliga-season-visualized/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2014-2015-bundesliga-season-visualized/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of the Bundesliga, particularly supporting Borussia Dortmund. I made this d3.js graph after the completion of the 2014-2015 season, namely as a means to show the fast decline and slow ascent of Dortmund throughout the season.
The link to the actual interactive graphic can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2014-2015 Bundesliga Season, Visualized (Part 2)</title>
      <link>/blog/2014-2015-bundesliga-season-visualized-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2014-2015-bundesliga-season-visualized-part-2/</guid>
      <description>As a extension of this graphic on the Bundesliga, I wanted to allow for different metrics to be selected. In this graphic, you can select a metric, which changes the y-axis of the graph.
The link to the actual interactive graphic can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100 Digits of Phi</title>
      <link>/blog/100-digits-of-phi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/100-digits-of-phi/</guid>
      <description>My name, Phi, also represents the &amp;lsquo;golden ratio&amp;rsquo;: &amp;#934; = 1.618. This visualization graphically depicts the number, with each digit being represented by a color and unit vector in the polar coordinate system.
The link to the actual interactive graphic can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>